begellhouse.com 2019-10-23

# Begell House - Begell House Privacy Policy

Begell House (BH) is dedicated to complying with data-protection regulations by recognizing the importance of protecting the information collected from Users in the operation of our web site. By submitting personal data meaning details you provide us when filling out our forms, e.g. your email address, order and billing information, and all data captured in authentication and tracking logs, will mean that you accept that such personal data will be gathered and stored in our databases. 

Reasonable steps are taken to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with the Begell House Privacy and Data Protection Policy. By using our web site and by registering for any of our services or products you agree to the practices defined herein.

We will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your personal data. This data will be used to provide you with the BH services and products you have ordered and will not be shared with other companies for marketing or similar purposes. We may occasionally use your information to inform you of new services and products related to those products/material you have ordered.

Authentication and tracking logs will be used to produce usage statistics and will not contain any personally identifiable information. BH reserves the right to have logs and databases analyzed by external service providers, in which case every effort will be made to protect the security, integrity and privacy of the data. Please keep in mind that we will not be responsible for personal data posted on any open forums or message boards.

## Cookies

Cookies, also known as an HTTP cookie, web cookie, or browser cookie, is usually a small piece of data sent from a web site and stored in a user's web browser while a user is browsing a web site. When the user browses the same web site in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the web site to notify the web site of the user's previous activity to enable the operator of the site make their visits more enjoyable or customize your experience. We may use cookies in a variety of ways, such as to collect information to help us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. We don't use cookies to collect and store individually-identifiable information. You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely.

To obtain detailed information concerning cookies you can go to www.aboutcookies.org which is a great resource for explaining how to easily delete or control cookies from any web site.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted to the BH website, please check periodically.

## Disclaimer

BH cannot take responsibility for information found on third party web sites that is beyond our control. We do try to provide links only to third-party web sites that comply with all applicable laws, regulations, and our own privacy standards. Please realize that the content on third-party web sites can change, at any time, without notice to BH, so therefore we cannot accept responsibility for, nor can we accept any liability for any information or opinion contained in any third-party web site.
